piccsy.com 2018-05-14

# Piccsy :: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

The following document outlines the policies that Groundwave Media Group Inc. enforce throughout the following domains 

  1. www.piccsy.com 
  2. www.recitethis.com 
  3. www.hellokisses.com 

### Our Commitment to your Privacy

Thank you for visiting Piccsy, located at http://www.piccsy.com, this website is operated and maintained by Groundwave Media Group Inc. The privacy of anonymous, pseudo-anonymous information and registered users is of the utmost importance to us. This policy describes the following 

  1. How, why and what information we collect about you via the Website. 
  2. How we use and with whom we share such collected information. 
  3. How you can attain access to, and update such information. 
  4. The choices you can make to control which information we can collect about you. 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, the information we collect about you or the practises that we employ, please contact us using the information provided. 

### The Information We Collect

#### Registration

  1. Website Account - In order to register for access to a Website Account, you must provide the following information 
  2. Facebook Account - When registering for a Website account via Facebook, we utilize your Facebook name and/or username to provide you with a valid username on Piccs. 
  3. Twitter Account - When registering for a Website account via Twitter, we utilize your Twitter username to provide you with a valid username for use on the relevant domain. 

Of the information collected through registration, we will never publicly expose or intentionally share your email address or password with any third parties (no matter how trustworthy they are!). 

#### Profile Information

In addition to the required information for the creation of an account, you may provide us with additional information about yourself in-order to personalise your publicly accessible Profile page. This includes 

  1. Name 
  2. Location 
  3. Website 
  4. Biography 
  5. Picture 

#### Anonymous Information

We also collect non-personal information about your usage of the website, for internal statistics and tracking only. We do not share this information with third parties, and ensure that information is never aggregated in a pseudo-anonymous manner, you (the user) can never identified through it. 

### How we collect information about you

We collect Personal Information and Anonymous Information about you in the following ways 

#### Registering an Account

In order for you to interact and personalise your experience on the website, we require the creation of an account in-order to store your interactions. The account is created directly through the website by the use of submitting a form; or through the social services Facebook or Twitter, information provided to us by these services are through an encrypted OAuth 1.0 token-based connection. 

#### Profile Customization

Once an account has been created for you, we provide you with the opportunity to customise your Profile page, by providing additional publicly accessible information about yourself. 

#### Public Display

Your profile picture, and certain publicly accessible information is attached to content that you have uploaded or directly interacted with, through the use of “Piccing” or “Adding to a Gallery”. 

This information, including your public Profile page is accessible to anonymous visitors and users of the website alike. 

#### Public Interactions

Through use of the website, you are able to indirectly interact, communicate approval of content and share information not just with us, but also with other visitors of the website and users of the service. This includes 

#### Cookies and Automated information collection

We utilize two technologies referred to as “Cookies” and “Localstorage” to collect and aggregate anonymous information about you and other users of the website. This information helps you to personalize your experience, and identify you as a return user of the website. We comply with EU Law concerning the usage and collection of Cookies; for detailed information about the information we collect through the use of Cookies and Localstorage, view our Cookies page: http://www.piccsy.com/cookies 

You may disable the anonymous collection of information through the use of Cookies and Localstorage, by using the information provided here, http://www.youronlinechoices.com/five-top-tips. 

#### Advertisements

Advertisements displayed on our website are delivered through the Doubleclick Google-based third party advertisement network. Note that cookies are used to collect information about your online trends by these services in-order to provide you with suitable and personalised adverts. 

If you wish to opt-out of the Doubleclick cookie tracking service, please use this page: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin/. 

For more information about how advertisers track your online activity, the following website provides useful information, http://www.youronlinechoices.com. 

### How we use information collected from you

We use the Personal Information that you provide, along with aggregated anonymous information in one or more of the following ways. 

#### How we use Your Personal Information

  1. To register, interact with and service your account. 
  2. For internal records, tracking and (ethical) business purposes. 
  3. To send you an optional weekly newsletter about trending activity on the website. 
  4. In order to contact, investigate and respond to you regarding questions, comments or technical support tickets. 
  5. To provide you with up-to-date information regarding upcoming and recently implemented changes to our website that may affect you or your account. 
  6. Unlike other websites, we DO NOT share your personal information with third-party advertising companies. 

#### How we use Anonymous Information

Anonymous Information contains usage and tracking statistics collected by visitors and users through the use of Cookies, Localstorage and HTTP header information. 

  1. To help improve and better target products and provided services for our users 
  2. To improve the overall user experience of the website 
  3. Analyze usage statistics, view trends and track singular page activity to 
  4. Create a weekly newsletter describing popular Images and trending public statistics 

### How we use information collected from you

We use the Personal Information that you provide, along with aggregated anonymous information in one or more of the following ways. 

####  How we use Your Personal Information 

  1. To register, interact with and service your account. 
  2. For internal records, tracking and (ethical) business purposes. 
  3. To send you an optional weekly newsletter about trending activity on the website. 
  4. In order to contact, investigate and respond to you regarding questions, comments or technical support tickets. 
  5. To provide you with up-to-date information regarding upcoming and recently implemented changes to our website that may affect you or your account. 
  6. Unlike other websites, we DO NOT share your personal information with third-party advertising companies. 

####  How we use Anonymous Information 

Anonymous Information contains usage and tracking statistics collected by visitors and users through the use of Cookies, Localstorage and HTTP header information. 

  1. To help improve and better target products and provided services for our users. 
  2. To improve the overall user experience of the website. 
  3. Analyze usage statistics, view trends and track singular page activity to; 
  4. Create a weekly newsletter describing popular Images and trending public statistics. 

### Sharing your information

#### Third-party Corporations

We never share your private personal information (your email) with anyone. Ever. 

We do not actively share your publicly accessible personal information with third-party corporations. 

#### Governments

In order to comply with safety, security and the law. We may disclose any information, including Personal information we deem necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or valid governmental request; or to enforce our rights or to protect the safety and security of the website for other users. 

#### Merger or Business Transition

In the event Groundwave Media Group Incorporated undergoes a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we may transfer your Personal Information to the successor organization in such transaction. If material changes to Groundwave Media Group Incorporated's privacy practices will occur as a result of the business transition, Groundwave Media Group will attempt to notify you via email and will post a notice on the Website alerting you to the business transition prior to transferring your Personal Information so that we can elect whether to delete your account. 

#### Third-Party Contractors

We may contract with third party companies to perform services on our behalf, including marketing assistance, e-mail delivery, hosting services, customer service, and data analysis. We require any third party service providers to maintain the confidentiality of the information disclosed to them and they are not permitted to use your Personal Information for any purpose other than to provide services to Groundwave Media Group. 

### How to access and update your information

You can access and update the information that you have provided to Groundwave Media Group as follows

  1. In order to adhere to the Data Protection Act, you may contact us at hello@piccsy.com and request to review, amend or delete the Personal Information collected by us, and/or request us to cease collecting Personal Information from you in the future. 
  2. If you have created an Account, you may review and make changes to certain parts of your Personal Information logging into your Account and updating your Account profile. 

### Links to third party web sites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Website nor the information or content contained therein. 

Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful or interesting to our users, or provided by other users to give you more information about themselves. Please remember that when you navigate away from the Website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. By your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on our Website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

### Our policy towards children

This Website contains mature content and is sometimes unintentionally displayed on the landing page. 

It is not intended for minors (as seen by the law of their residing country) and we do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from such minors. Minors under the age of 13 should not use our Website or our online services at any time. In the event that we learn that we have inadvertently gathered Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will use reasonable efforts to erase such information from our records. 

### Security of your information

We implement reasonable administrative, technical and physical security measures to protect the security of your information both online and offline, and we are committed to the protection of customer information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information to those employees we reasonably believe need such information do their jobs. 

Your User Account information is protected by the password you use to access your online account. 

It is important that you protect and maintain the security of your User Account and that you immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your User Account. If you forget your password, you may request a new password by following this link: http://www.piccsy.com/lostpassword/ 

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches of the Website, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure. 

We cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. We urge you to take steps to keep your Personal Information safe (including your User Account password), and log out of your User Account after use. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

If we decide to make material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will attempt to notify you and other users of the Website by sending a notice to the email address provided to us and/or by placing a notice on our Website. You should periodically check the Website for such notices. 

This privacy policy can change at any time. 

### Contact us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy and/or practices, please send an email to hello@piccsy.com.
